/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data9_3', {
    title: '9.3 Build an Equivalent Fraction',
    path: '9.3-build-an-equivalent-fraction',
    children: [{
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a denominator of 20.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{4}}}}{\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a numerator of 21.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{21}}{\\fracstr{18}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{3}}}}{\\frac{\\input{21}}{\\fracstr{18}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{6}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{21}}{\\fracstr{18}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{9}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a numerator of 22.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{22}}{\\fracstr{18}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{9}}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{2}}}}{\\frac{\\input{22}}{\\fracstr{18}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{11}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{2}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{22}}{\\fracstr{18}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{8}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a denominator of 24.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{33}}{\\fracstr{24}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{8}}}{\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{3}}}}{\\frac{\\input{33}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{11}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{33}}{\\fracstr{24}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a denominator of 12.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}{\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{3}}}}{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{8}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a numerator of 12.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{32}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{8}}}{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{4}}}}{\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{32}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{12}}{\\fracstr{32}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{10}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a numerator of 35.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{35}}{\\fracstr{70}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{10}}}{\\frac{\\input{7}}{\\input{7}}}}{\\frac{\\input{35}}{\\fracstr{70}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{7}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{35}}{\\fracstr{70}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{15}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a denominator of 90.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{60}}{\\fracstr{90}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{15}}}{\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\input{6}}}}{\\frac{\\input{60}}{\\fracstr{90}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{10}}{\\fracstr{15}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{6}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{60}}{\\fracstr{90}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{12}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a numerator of 18.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{18}}{\\fracstr{24}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{12}}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{2}}}}{\\frac{\\input{18}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{2}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{18}}{\\fracstr{24}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Build an Equivalent Fraction',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Start with the fraction \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{25}}}}{\\row{\\str{ and build an equivalent fraction that has a denominator of 100.}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{100}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Multiply numerator and denominator by the same number: \xA0}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\buildequivfracs{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{25}}}{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{4}}}}{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{100}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{25}}}{\\str{\xA0 times \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\str{\xA0 equals \xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{24}}{\\fracstr{100}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
